<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Archaeology on HIST3000|CLCV3000</title>
    <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Archaeology on HIST3000|CLCV3000</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Original content by Shawn Graham licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#39;license&#39; href=&#39;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#39;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a rel=&#39;license&#39; href=&#39;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#39;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#39;Creative Commons License logo&#39; style=&#39;border-width:0&#39; src=&#39;https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-nc/4.0/88x31.png&#39; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;Site logo &#39;archaeological information&#39; by corpus delicti, GR, The Noun Project.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:15:05 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://hist3000.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Module 1 Capturing/Creating</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Getting Started 
Goals for this week  getting our Github accounts set up and making our first log entries getting Hypothes.is set up getting Zotero installed getting a sense of what digital archaeology is; also, &amp;lsquo;failing gloriously&amp;rsquo;  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  An Introduction to Digital Archaeology ODATE, sections 1.1 to 1.1.2 Cook, Katherine, and Beth. Compton. Canadian Digital Archaeology: On Boundaries and Futures. Invited submission for special anniversary issue of Canadian Journal of Archaeology 42: 38-45.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M1 Wk2: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/2/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/2/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Field work and ethical data collection Goals for this week  Find a local historic graveyard (current graveyard is OK) Begin recording at least 10 gravestones Create a digital map of the site  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  Cook, Katherine. 2018 Open Data as Public Archaeology: The Monumental Archive Project. AP: Online Journal of Public Archaeology 3: 177-194. link Lacy, Robyn S. 2018. Public Engagement through Burial Landscapes: Cupids and Ferryland, Newfoundland.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M1 Wk3: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/3/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:42 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/3/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Field work and ethical data collection II Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  Cook, Katherine. 2018 Negotiating Memory: Funerary Commemoration as Social Change in Barbados. African and Black Diaspora: An International Journal. link Pillatt, Toby. et al. 2020 The Burial Space Research Database (Data Paper), Internet Archaeology 55. link Gupta, Neha. 2017. Geographic Visualization in Archaeology. Journal of Archaeological Method and Theory 24, 852–885 link Baxter, Jane Eva.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M1 Wk4: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/4/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/4/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Consolidation Pause I Goals for this week  Use this time to catch up on anything you didn&amp;rsquo;t read, to try some of the exercises over again, and to consolidate what you&amp;rsquo;ve achieved so far.  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Do  Create a short consolidation document that reflects on this first module and your growth. Discuss at least one &amp;lsquo;fail&amp;rsquo; and one &amp;lsquo;win&amp;rsquo;. Explicitly situate your discussion with reference to the readings and annotations by the class as a whole.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Module 2: Considering/Critiquing</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/5/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:09 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/5/instructions/</guid>
        <description>What Gets Counted, Counts 
Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  ‘What gets counted, counts’. Draft chapter from Data Feminism by Catherine D’Ignazio and Lauren Klein link Labrador, Angela. 2012. Ontologies of the Future and Interfaces for All: Archaeological Databases for the Twenty-First Century. Archaeologies 8,236–249 link Cook, Katherine, et al. 2018. Teaching Open Science: Published Data and Digital Literacy in Archaeology Classrooms.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M2 Wk6: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/6/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:09 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/6/instructions/</guid>
        <description>The Contexts of Digital and Other Archaeologies Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  White, William and Catherine Draycott. 2020 Why the Whiteness of Archaeology Is a Problem. SAPIENS link Perry, Sara and James Taylor. 2018. Theorising the Digital: A Call to Action for the Archaeological Community. In Oceans of Data: Proceedings of the 44th Conference on Computer Applications and Quantitative Methods in Archaeology, Mieko Matsumoto &amp;amp; Espen Uleberg, eds.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M2 Wk7: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/7/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/7/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Futures of Digital Archaeology Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  Huggett, Jeremy. 2017 The Apparatus of Digital Archaeology, Internet Archaeology 44. link
Dawson, Ian, and Reilly, Paul. 2019. “Messy Assemblages, Residuality and Recursion within a Phygital Nexus” Epoiesen link AND RESPONSE by Rachel Opitz link Morgan, Colleen. 2019. Avatars, Monsters, and Machines: A Cyborg Archaeology. European Journal of Archaeology 22.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Working Safely</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/2/safework/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/2/safework/</guid>
        <description>If any of the instructions below are unclear, annotate this page with hypothesis while being logged into our course reading group. If you spot someone asking for help and you can offer advice, respond to the annotation. Introduction This week, I am asking you to go out into your community and find a historic graveyard to work on. There was a graveyard in the middle of a field not far from the childhood home of a friend of mine.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M2 Wk8: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/8/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/8/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Consolidation Pause II Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Do  Use this time to catch up on anything you didn&amp;rsquo;t read, to try some of the exercises over again, and to consolidate what you&amp;rsquo;ve achieved so far.  With tech work, if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t come together in about 30 minutes, it won&amp;rsquo;t come in an hour. So take a break.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Graveyard Project Rationale</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/2/rationale/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/2/rationale/</guid>
        <description>Annotate this page with hypothesis while being logged into our course reading group with connections to other things you&amp;rsquo;ve read or thought about during your studies. If you spot an interesting annotation by someone else and it strikes a chord, respond generously to the annotation. Introduction I wanted you to have some experience of collecting data, and of how data models (or our expectations of what we&amp;rsquo;ll find) influence the subsequent work that we can do with the information that we collect.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Setting up your Github</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/github/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/github/</guid>
        <description>If any of the instructions below are unclear, annotate this page with hypothesis while being logged into our course reading group. If you spot someone asking for help and you can offer advice, respond to the annotation. Introduction Github is a code sharing website often used by digital historians. &amp;lsquo;Git&amp;rsquo; is a program that takes snapshots of the current state of a folder, and stores them in sequence, allowing you to revert your changes to an earlier state.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Module 3: Communicating</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/9/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/9/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Communicating Digital Archaeology Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  ‘The Numbers Don’t Speak for Themselves’ Draft chapter from Data Feminism by Catherine D’Ignazio and Lauren Klein link Ben Marwick, Carl Boettiger &amp;amp; Lincoln Mullen. 2018. Packaging Data Analytical Work Reproducibly Using R (and Friends), The American Statistician, 72:1, 80-88, link Perry, Sara, Roussou, Maria, Mirashrafi, Sophia S., Katifori, A.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Setting up your Hypothesis</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/hypothesis/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/hypothesis/</guid>
        <description>While watching this video, turn on the closed captions.
Create an account at hypothes.is:
Get the Chrome app or the Firefox bookmarklet:
Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re logged in:
Then join our HIST3000|CLCV3000 reading group. If you happen to be reading something, and see an existing annotation that interests you, hit the &amp;lsquo;reply&amp;rsquo; button on the annotation to start a conversation! Sometimes, the person to whom you&amp;rsquo;re replying might be a previous year&amp;rsquo;s student, but that&amp;rsquo;s ok; they might enter into conversation with you.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M3 Wk10: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/10/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/10/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Communities Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  Morgan, Colleen, Robert Carter, Michal Michalski. 2016. The Origins of Doha Project: Online Digital Heritage Remediation and Public Outreach in a Vanishing Pearling Town in the Arabian Gulf. CHNT 20: Conference on Cultural Heritage and New Technologies November 2-4. 1-8. link Richardson, L.-J., 2019. Using Social Media as a Source for Understanding Public Perceptions of Archaeology: Research Challenges and Methodological Pitfalls.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Setting up your Zotero</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/zotero/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/zotero/</guid>
        <description>Zotero is a piece of software for managing your research. When it is installed, it can extract metadata from websites or pdfs (when these have metadata) and store the information in your very own library. Zotero can be connected to Word or Google Docs so that when it is time to insert a reference, you can select the reference from your library - and then get the machine to automatically format/update your bibliography against whatever citation style you use.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M3 Wk11: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/11/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/11/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Storytelling Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Read  Perry, Sara. 2019. The Enchantment of the Archaeological Record. European Journal of Archaeology. 22.3, 354-371link González-Tennant, Edward. 2010. Virtual Archaeology and Digital Storytelling: A Report from Rosewood, Florida. The African Diaspora Archaeology Network, September 2010 Newsletter. link Alex Fitzpatrick. 2019. No Margins, No Word Counts, No Masters! Experimenting With &amp;lsquo;Zines for Archaeological Outreach 2019 #PATC link Vrettakis, Ektor et al.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Getting started with Discord</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/discord/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/discord/</guid>
        <description>What is Discord? You can download Discord here or you can use it in a broswer.
You will receive an invitation email in your Carleton account. It expires after one day, so do join once you get it. It will ask to verify your email; check your spam folder.
Once you&amp;rsquo;re in, there&amp;rsquo;s a welcome message with a reaction emoji at the end - click on the thumbs up to confirm that you&amp;rsquo;ve read the message.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>M3 Wk12: Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/12/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:37 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/12/instructions/</guid>
        <description>Consolidation Pause III Goals for this week  TODO TODO TODO TODO  Listen Feed for the podcast here.
Do  Use this time to catch up on anything you didn&amp;rsquo;t read, to try some of the exercises over again, and to consolidate what you&amp;rsquo;ve achieved so far.  With tech work, if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t come together in about 30 minutes, it won&amp;rsquo;t come in an hour. So take a break.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>1. Course Description</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/1-coursedescription/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:39:09 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/1-coursedescription/</guid>
        <description>HIST3000|CLCV3000 Fall 2020 Department of History, Carleton University Once the excavation is over, what happens to the information created through archaeological research? How do archaeologists use digital technologies on site, in the lab, or on the web? This course explores the intersection of digital technologies and computing with archaeology. We will explore the ways theory gets embedded into computation; perhaps there is even a theory of digital archaeology? We will explore how digital technologies allow us to ask questions that would otherwise be impossible to ask.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2. Learning Outcomes</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/2-learning-outcomes/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:38:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/2-learning-outcomes/</guid>
        <description>Questions I developed this course with a couple of questions in mind, things I wanted to know the answers to. Digital archaeology - what the hell is it, anyway? What is it for? Is it just a &amp;lsquo;follower&amp;rsquo;, repurposing other tools &amp;amp; techniques, a supporting skill for &amp;lsquo;real&amp;rsquo; archaeology? Let&amp;rsquo;s set ourselves some grand challenges.
This course is a formalized exploration of these questions; I do not know the answers! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to figure these out with you.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3. Course Calendar</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/3-schedule/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:38:48 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/3-schedule/</guid>
        <description>Each week involves completing to the best of your ability various exercises; you will document your progress in a weekly log that you will keep online. Log entries are required to be completed by the Sunday evening at the end of the relevant work. A final reflection piece is due at the end of the course. See the assessment page for further details.
Some exercises are collaborative for the class as a whole.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>4. Assessment</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/4-assessment/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:38:59 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/4-assessment/</guid>
        <description>There is no midterm. There is no final exam. Weekly Work Evidence Therefore, I am looking for the following kinds of evidence (each week will specify what needs to be done):
 logs/lab notebook entry that keep track of what you actually did reflection on that process engagement with the materials and your classmates (which might be demonstrated many different ways) evidence for your growth as a scholar over this course  At the end of each week by Sunday evening, you will provide to me through a form that can be found on each weekly page the links to your evidence for me to consider.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>And We&#39;re Off!</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/blog/update1/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/blog/update1/</guid>
        <description>(click the title to see the full post, not just this preview)
Welcome! Check your Carleton email account this morning for a note from me about getting started in the class.
There are no zoom meetings in this class (balloons, confetti, streamers fall from ceiling, much rejoicing, etc).
There is a discord server for a class social space and for video, audio chat &amp;amp; screensharing (which is useful when things go wrong and you want someone to look at what you&amp;rsquo;re doing).</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>5. Common Regulations</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/5-commonregs/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/5-commonregs/</guid>
        <description>The following are the University regulations common to all History courses. COPIES OF WRITTEN WORK SUBMITTED Always retain for yourself a copy of all essays, term papers, written assignments or take-home tests submitted in your courses.
PLAGIARISM The University Senate defines plagiarism as “presenting, whether intentionally or not, the ideas, expression of ideas or work of others as one’s own.” This can include:
 reproducing or paraphrasing portions of someone else’s published or unpublished material, regardless of the source, and presenting these as one’s own without proper citation or reference to the original source; submitting a take home examination, essay, laboratory report or other assignment written, in whole or in part, by someone else; using ideas or direct, verbatim quotations, or paraphrased material, concepts, or ideas without appropriate acknowledgment in any academic assignment; using another’s data or research findings; failing to acknowledge sources through the use of proper citations when using another’s works and/or failing to use quotation marks; handing in &amp;ldquo;substantially the same piece of work for academic credit more than once without prior written permission of the course instructor in which the submission occurs.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>6. Contacting Dr. Graham</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/6-contact/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/6-contact/</guid>
        <description>Dr. Graham can be found online at
shawn dot graham at carleton dot ca
or on Twitter at @electricarchae.
He will be present in our class discord server every day.
If we ever get out of quarantine, and you&amp;rsquo;re in Ottawa, he often haunts the Library coffeeshop.
Online Office Hours Dr. Graham will be present in our Discord server every Wednesday from 1 until 3, and quite possibly the evenings too.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>7. Colophon</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/7-colophon/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/7-colophon/</guid>
        <description>As a general philosophy of learning, I do not aim for coverage. Rather, I am trying to help you learn the skills that you will need to uncover whatever aspect of method and thought that will help you with your research goals. A big part of that is trying to teach how to deal with what might feel like &amp;lsquo;failure&amp;rsquo;, on first blush. I want you to swing for the bleachers, and not to be afraid of whiffing on the ball.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>8. Reuse</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/8-reuse/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/docs/8-reuse/</guid>
        <description>Original content by Shawn Graham, is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.
Please feel free to reuse exercises in your own course materials, with a link back to the original page.
Corrections, modifications, additions are welcome; please fork, and then modify accordingly. Once you&amp;rsquo;re ready, make a pull request. The original repository is at [https://github.com/shawngraham/hist3908](https://github.com/shawngraham/hist3908.
All contributions will be duly credited.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Asking for help</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/help/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:51 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/1/help/</guid>
        <description>Help! Things have gone wrong! Montparnasse Derailment, 1895
Things are going to go wrong. Things are going to break. Instructions will seem vague or incomplete - or worse, I will have indeed forgotten to tell you something crucial.
Or worse, I&amp;rsquo;ve made an assumption about your understanding, and left things unsaid that needed to be made explicit. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of this, in the digital world, in fact.
This week, you learned a bit about Git and Github.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Final Submission Instructions</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/12-5/instructions/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:10:09 +0900</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/week/12-5/instructions/</guid>
        <description>The Last Bit The last bit of the course is the Exit Ticket.
Listen Do The format of the exit ticket is up to you. You craft a statement reflecting on where you started and where you’ve gotten to, and you will indicate how you feel you’ve done against the learning outcomes. You may, if you wish, indicate what you think your letter grade ought to be, and why.
[more]</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Placeholder Text</title>
        <link>https://hist3000.netlify.app/blog/placeholder/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>shawn.graham@carleton.ca (Dr. Shawn Graham)</author>
        <guid>https://hist3000.netlify.app/blog/placeholder/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Click title to see the full Post&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de&lt;br /&gt;
pectora summo. Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice&lt;br /&gt;
subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc&lt;br /&gt;
caluere tempus&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>